https://www.nickys-nursery.co.uk/privacy.php?osCsid=64737dd00686b6d156e95acfbd52c1e0

SocialFacebookTwitterGoogle +CompanyContact usConditions of useShipping and returnsPrivacy informationAccountCreate accountLoginOrder historyYour cart is empty
Login
Home
New Products
Shipping
Seeds
WHAT TO SOW
CHILLI SEEDS
SWEET PEPPERS
Catalog
»
Privacy Notice
»
Privacy Notice
Nicky's Nursery Ltd respect your privacy and the information you share with us to fulfil your order. This privacy policy is for this website www.nickys-nursery.co.uk and served by Nicky's Nursery Ltd and governs the privacy of its user's who choose to use it.
The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations & requirements of the user's, the website and website owners. Furthermore the way this website processes, stores and protects user data and information will also be detailed within this policy.
The Website
This website and its owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its user's throughout their visiting experience. This website complies to all UK national laws and requirements for user privacy.
Use of Cookies
This website uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website. Where applicable this website uses a cookie control system allowing the user on their first visit to the website to allow or disallow the use of cookies on their computer / device. This complies with recent legislation requirements for websites to obtain explicit consent from users before leaving behind or reading files such as cookies on a users computer / device. Cookies are small files saved to the users computers hard drive that track, save and store information about the users interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website. Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website on to their computers hard drive they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from this website and its external serving vendors. This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computers hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information. You can read Google's privacy policy here for further information [ http://www.google.com/privacy.html ]. Other cookies may be stored to your computers hard drive by external vendors when this website uses referral programs, sponsored links or adverts. Such cookies are used for conversion and referral tracking and typically expire after 30 days, though some may take longer. No personal information is stored, saved or collected.
Contact & Communication
Users contacting this website and/or its owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use, as detailed in the Data Protection Act 1998. Every effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process but advise users using such form to email processes that they do so at their own risk. This website and its owners use any information submitted to provide you with further information about the products / services they offer or to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have submitted. All details are submitted securely via SSL.
Personal Data
The details we hold will include Name, address, phone number, email, ip address, products ordered and order history.
The Data we hold above is used solely to process your order. The order History is not used for Marketing, it's for you the customer to see your previous orders.
We do not use any of your information for promotional emails, marketing, promoting our website, or to contact you about any offers, we do not send out News Letters or discount codes or coupons. All our Offers and New products can be viewed online.
Your details are not passed on to any third parties for any reason other than processing
your order.
We will only contact you when:-
a)	You place an order online, we will send you a confirmation email for you to check the details are correct.
b)	 We notify you by email when we accept your order and start to process it.
c)	When we dispatch your order
d)	 If you contact us for further information about the products we sell
e)	 If you require a quote or availability of a product
Payment for orders
We use Third Parties:-
WorldPay to process payment for our orders, WorldPay is a payment service provided by WorldPay Limited, to enable customers to make their online payments.
PayPal to process payment for our orders, PayPal is a payment service provided by PayPal, to enable customers to make their online payments.
We have no access to your credit or debit card details.
Removing Customers Details
Under UK tax law we have to keep your basic personal Data for a minimum of 7 years (The Data we use to process and dispatch your order).
After this period you have the right to have your Data deleted, this means you would not have access to previous orders. Please contact us to remove your Data.
The right of Access to Data and Rectification.
The Data we hold is available for you to see online in Your Account, this data is the form you filled in when you placed the order, we hold no other Data. If you see any errors in your data you have the option of rectifying it yourself through your account or contacting us to rectify it.
Dispatch Of Goods
Dispatch of goods is via Royal Mail, Courier or third parties for direct dispatch of goods who we share your name and address with, to enable them to deliver your order.
Social Media Platforms
Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and its owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively. Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate / engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details. This website nor its owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email. This website may use social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question. Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account.
Edited & customised by:
Nicky's Nursery Ltd May 2018
33, Fairfield road,
Broadstairs.
Kent
CT102JU
Continue
Categories Seeds->Garden Games->Garden Sundries->
Bestsellers Coriander Calypso 155 seedsTomato Sungold 10 seedsChilli Padron 20 seedsTomato Gardeners Delight 50 seedsTomato Heirloom Mix 10 seedsEntsai Water Spinach or Ong Choy Ipomoea aquatica 75 seedsChilli Carolina Reaper 10 seedsChilli Thai Dragon 15 seedsChamomile Lawn Anthemis Nobilis 1000 seedsYellow Rattle 1 gram Av 340 seeds
What's New? Scabiosa. Merlot Red
50 seeds£1.95
Products
Chilli Peppers
Flower
Vegetable
Tomato
Herb
Nicky's Nursery Ltd.
33 Fairfield Road,
Broadstairs,
Kent,
CT10 2JU,
United Kingdom.
Phone 01843 600972
Copyright © 2020 Nickys Nursery Ltd
Powered by osCommerce | Designed on Mini Template System
